<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volvo 850 Warwagon</title>
    <description>Issue and modifaction log. Database of issue/solution articles.</description>
    <link>http://volvo850wagon.tk/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://volvo850wagon.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 13:11:34 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 13:11:34 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Trying out Techno Textile Cleaner</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/e8QMBzTEAyQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-channel-new-challanges&quot;&gt;New channel, new challanges!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A while ago I fell in love with this brick of a car. Namely a Volvo 850 estate!
This car has a 2.5l engine and is equipped with a dual fuel system. Since prices on gas are very high out here, I can always easy the pain on my wallet by filling her up with LPG.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Sturdy, intimidating and still fast as fuck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video above is actually more of an excuse to create a video. I need to scrub off the editor rust, since I did enjoy some long editing sessions back when I had a Windows ME that could barely run anything decent to the DELL laptop that recently died with Windows Vista running on top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not going too in depth in this. Just to get you the idea of what kind of tier my gear was in back then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Already by making my first video I’m testing different render settings, presentation techniques and figuring out how to introduce and end my videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, this video won’t have a decent outro just because I have no clips to show about previous ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-product-tested&quot;&gt;The product, tested&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum it up, it didn’t do any good of a job. You could see on a white cloth that it rubbed of some grimy stuff. I bet you could get the same result by rubbing the cloth without this product. It didn’t cost anything really. 2 euros at max I think in a local cheap ass store. Not to lay a burn on this store. They actually DO have stuff that is very useful for a good price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;feedback&quot;&gt;Feedback&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the very start of a new beginning so don’t hold back on me in the comment section below. But I advice you to keep your commentary somewhat constructive so I can actually benefit from the info.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://volvo850wagon.tk/trying-out-techno-textile-cleaner/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://volvo850wagon.tk/trying-out-techno-textile-cleaner/</guid>
        
        <category>cheap</category>
        
        <category>textile cleaner</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>cleanup</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First vlog ever</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/jXp4QsfvqoE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bad-karma&quot;&gt;Bad karma?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was rather dubious about the idea of maintaining a blog and vlog at the same time but I finally got to the point to kick this off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While recording this video, not everything went according to plan though. The plan was to record my day in my Volvo, while doing some mods and touch ups at first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along the way, my wallet thought it was a good idea to stay put on my roof while leaving a store parking lot. Long story short, I lost it and somebody was kind enough to bring it in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you’re reading this, thanks for not emptying out my wallet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before the event of me actually getting contacted that my wallet was found, I went totally nuts. In my head I actually went to hell and back, thinking about the &lt;strong&gt;lost cash, my ID, driving license and the freaking CARD-STOP process&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-recording-process&quot;&gt;The recording process&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never did I even record myself for something serious on YouTube and you’ll probably notice that while watching this one. Even when I’m aware of that, it’s still very accomplishing to do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You wont see vlogs every day because there are other videos aside from the vlogs I will need to edit.&lt;/strong&gt; Also, when writing this I’m still working on the basic structure of this website, other hobbies, work, friends to keep in touch with. You don’t actually work 24/7 on YouTube content and I really don’t get it yet how the regulars do this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;editing&quot;&gt;Editing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the day I really liked to edit videos in Sony Vegas and Adobe Premiere. Now that I’ve installed Premiere again I can’t bear to notice how much things has changed. So the first task was picking up the ropes again of the editing process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, there are a lot more kinds of software in the Adobe suite used for video media. Recently tried out Prelude, a piece of software that encourages you to create a rough cut before diving into the more complicated Premiere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I’ll talk about my workflow later on but until then I’ll keep learning more about it. Also to prevent misinforming you peeps!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thanks for supporting me by reading this article and don’t hesitate to leave some feedback (positive or negative I don’t care) to help me improve.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://volvo850wagon.tk/first-vlog-ever/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://volvo850wagon.tk/first-vlog-ever/</guid>
        
        <category>first</category>
        
        <category>vlog</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
